# Amin Razavi

 ¶ +989360705198
 | ■ m.a.razavi78@gmail.com | 
 | ★ amin-razavi.ir

## Personal Profile \_\_\_\_

A Bachelor's student at the University of Tehran, with 2+ years of experience in full-stack development in **Dybug** company. Primarily, interested in Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence and Data Mining. Now, actively looking for research opportunities as either an MSc or a PhD student.

### **Education**

#### University of Tehran (Best university of Iran generally and in computer science field)

Tehran, Iran

Bachelor of computer science

Sept 2018 - Current

• **GPA:** 3.26/4

#### Iranian University Entrance Exam(Konkur)

Tehran, Iran

July 2018

Before bachelor

• **Rank:** 388 among 144437 applicants

Alavi Tehran, Iran High School Sept 2014 - July 2018

• **GPA:** 19.85/20

## Scholarships And Certifications \_\_\_\_\_

**Scholarship** for study as a bachelor student from University of Tehran

**2 years Scholarship** for rank of Iranian University Entrance Exam (Konkur) from University of Tehran

**Certificate of Teaching Swim** this certification was given in summer of 2017

### Research Interests

\_\_ .... Related Courses ....

Machine Learning	Deep learning	currently studying
Artificial Intelligence	Statistical Methods	currently studying
Deep Learning	Artificial Intelligence	18/20
Supervised Learning	Programming	18.75/20

• Speech Recognition
• Speech Recognition
• Handwriting Recognition
• Data Mining 16.73/20

17.62/20

• NLP

Data Mining 14.5/20 Linear Algebra 15.5/20

Data Mining

**Probability 1** 15/20

# **University Projects**

**Scientific calculations** (by the help of one of my teachers in ML field)

**Description AI** Recognized pattern of some cancer cells

Natural Inspired Algorithms Developed a basic neural network

**Data Mining** Extracted some Association Rules and generated Classification on a dataset

**Assembly** Implemented a calculator with 4 main operations

**Assembly** Designed a Morris Mano basic computer in Logisim software

Advanced programming Created Tank game, system of ordering in cafe (both object oriented base) using Java

**Languages of Programming** Made Tic-tac-toe game with Rust

**Basic programming** Developed and deployed a website by Django

## **Work Experience**

#### Developed a data analyzer app

for students of Alavi high school

- Technical Skills: Python (Djnago, Numpy), SQL Server, chart.js, Git
- Soft Skills: Problem Solving, Teamwork, Time Management, Communication

#### **Developed a notification system**

for SMS and Telegram

- Technical Skills: Python (Djnago, DRF), PostgresSQL, API and CRUD, Git
- · Soft Skills: Problem Solving, Time Management

#### Designed and developed an automation

for factory of ScarfBank

- Technical Skills: Python (Djnago, DRF), PostgresSQL, API and CRUD, Git
- Soft Skills: Agile, Pattern designing, Writing code structures, Problem Solving, Time Management, Communication

#### **Developed and deployed Whatsapp engine**

June 2022 - current

September 2020 - January 2021

February 2021 - August 2021

September 2021 - May 2022

for Odoo ERP

- Technical Skills: Python (Djnago, DRF), JS (fastify), API, Git
- Soft Skills: Pattern designing, Writing code structures, Problem Solving, Communication

## **Teaching Experience**

- Tutor of Python programming for 6 month
- Tutor of Statistics and probability lesson for a bachelor student for 4 month
- · Tutor of Math for high school students for 4 month
- Tutor of Arabic for a high school student for 5 month

### $Skills_{-}$

### **Programming:**

- Python: Pandas, PyTorch, Tensorflow, NumPy, Django, DRF
- Java
- Assembly
- Rust
- R
- JavaScript
- HTML/CSS
- SQL

### **Soft Skills:**

- Git
- Linux LaTeX

#### Docker

### Miscellaneous:

- Agile
- writing
- · giving speech
- teaching
- playing tennis
- playing soccer

# Languages

Persian Mother tongue

**English** IELTS currently studying. Expected to get minimum 7 out of 9

professional level in academic Arabic **Arabic** 

# **Hobbies and Interests**

programming solving enigmas and puzzles playing and watching Tennis playing Soccer

reading researching watching movies

travelling with family and friends

## Refrences

Name: Dr. Bagher BabaAli Email: babaali@ut.ac.ir

**Location** College of Science / School of Mathematics, Statistics and Computer Science, University of Tehran, Tehran, Iran.

Name: Dr. Mojtaba Mojtahedi Email: mojtaba.mojtahedi@ut.ac.ir

**Location** College of Science / School of Mathematics, Statistics and Computer Science, University of Tehran, Tehran, Iran.

Name: Dr. Hedieh Sajedi Email: hhsajedi@ut.ac.ir

**Location** College of Science / School of Mathematics, Statistics and Computer Science, University of Tehran, Tehran, Iran.